♪ In the not too
distant future ♪
♪ Next Sunday A.D ♪
♪ There was a guy named Joel ♪
♪ Not too different
from you or me ♪
♪ He worked at
Gizmonic Institute ♪
♪ Just another face
in a red jump suit ♪
♪ He did a good job
cleaning up the place ♪
♪ But his bosses didn't like him
so they shot him into space ♪
♪ We'll send him cheesy movies ♪
♪ The worst we can find ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ He'll have to sit
and watch them all ♪
♪ Then we'll monitor his mind ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Now keep in mind
Joel can't control ♪
♪ When the movies begin or end ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Because he used
those special parts ♪
♪ To make his robot friends ♪
♪ Robot roll call Cambot ♪
- Pan left.
♪ Gypsy ♪
- Hi Girls.
♪ Tom Servo ♪
- What a cool guy.
♪ Crooooooow ♪
♪ If you're wondering how
he eats and breathes ♪
♪ And other science facts ♪
♪ La la la ♪
♪ Then repeat to yourself
its just a show ♪
♪ I should really just relax ♪
♪ For Mystery Science
Theater 3000. ♪
(door slams)
- [Announcer] 30 second
to commercial sign.
- Hi everybody, I'm
Joel as you know
and I'm on the
satellite of love here.
We're trapped in out of space.
Just got done
cleaning up the robots
for the experiment this week.
All nice and clean,
there you go.
- [Announcer] Commercial
sign in 15 seconds.
- Okay I guess we got a
commercial coming up real soon
and we're expecting a call from
the evil scientists as well
so you might want
to stick around.
- [Announcer] Commercial sign
in five, four, three, two.
Commercial sign now.
- Stick around,
we'll be right back.
(upbeat music)
- A cow.
- A bowl of Quisp.
- A Gutenberg printing press.
- Oh, the first level ROM card
of the Cray-1 super
computer generation C 1987.
- Right.
- Yes, yes.
- All right.
Hey, the scientists are calling.
- Come in Joel, my
little spunk dumpling.
- Hey sirs, is it time for
the invention exchange?
- No, it's time for
the AAU swim meet.
Yes it's time for the
invention exchange.
- There's a lot of sparky.
- All right sirs.
This week I've got a new
way of juggling water.
Okay, you're going
to help me Crow.
You're going to pitch to me.
So take this turkey baster.
Carry it over there.
Take it over that away.
Okay and I've got these
two ping pong paddles.
Okay, with special
surfaces that repel water.
Okay and Crow, on
the count of three
I want you to shoot a
jet of water here, okay?
- [Crow] Okey dokey.
- Ready?
One,
two,
three.
- Nice shot.
- Arc it up a little bit Crow,
on the count of three, let's go.
One,
two,
three.
Perfect, good.
Got it, okay.
See, look it.
I'm juggling water you guys.
- Cool.
- See.
Under the legs.
- Wow.
- Over the back, here we go.
Hey, just like that.
See?
Whoops, dropped it.
What do you think sirs?
- Oh, I've seen more
impressive tricks
on a box of Cracker Jacks.
- Well there are those
little tattoo things
you just leak on.
- Larry, Larry.
Now our invention this week
combines the ARDI effect
of the old Etch A Sketch
with the educational payoff
of Uncle Milty's Ant Farm.
We call it the Insecta Sketch.
(mumbles)
- What we've done is we've taken
the normal directional
capabilities of the ant
and scramble them with an
ultra sonic directional device.
A little guidance
system of our own.
See, I wrote my name.
(Larry laughs)
- Yes, and like its predecessor,
it clears with a shake.
Very nice Larry.
Now make me a picture
of Jokey Smurf.
- Okay.
I'd love to.
- Well, what do you think?
- I think it could really
bruise a child's tender psyche.
- Thank you.
Well, our movie this week
is called Project Moon Base,
and it features a
group of astronauts
almost as an ape
as you are Joel.
- And a plot as
weak as herbal tea.
- Yes, but first how
about a double dip
of our old friend Commando Cody
and the radar men from the moon.
(Larry chuckles)
(mumbling)
Interesting reaction.
What do you think Larry?
- I think I'm almost done.
See, I just gotta get the
little curve Smurf head.
- Giving me this.
(Larry chuckles)
Taste the pain buddy.
- Enjoy.
(loud beeping)
(Joel mumbling)
(doors creaking)
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Did you really
think it was better?
- [Tom] I think you
are much better.
The water dragon was
really pretty solid.
- [Crow] Definitely.
Cool.
Hey, a new character.
- [Joel] Yeah.
- [Tom] Yeah right.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] George Wallace in
his pre-gubernatorial days.
- [Joel] Clayton Moore
before Lone Ranger days.
- [Crow] And Dale Van Sickle.
He never made a bad film.
- [Joel] But Noel Cravat did.
Ronald Davidson, John
Davidson's smarter brother.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] And Franklin Adreon.
- [Joel] Hey, come on.
- [Crow] Close.
- [Tom] Fred C. Brannon.
Chapter Seven.
Camouflaged Destruction.
Commando Cody learns
that Graber and Daly
are in Clark mountain.
They go after them
through Zagnut Valley.
(Crow laughs)
Watch me, catch me
try to catch me.
I'm a little rabbit.
(Tom laughs)
(dramatic music)
- When Cody gets here,
give yourself up.
Try not to get too close to me.
- But look I--
- Don't argue.
Do what I tell you.
- [Joel] And wet your
lips, straighten your tie.
- Don't move.
- [Crow] Oh, I mean you
can move a little bit.
You can breathe and stuff.
- [Joel] Montana looks left.
- Drop your gun.
- [Joel] He's open,
fires away and it's incomplete.
Oh, that could have
been his rotator cuff
orbiting toward earth.
- [Crow] Wow.
- [Joel] Cool.
- [Tom] Wow!
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Meanwhile, back
at the Cody Institute
for people almost
die every week.
- I got the flying suit under
control just before I crushed,
but I'd lost my gun.
When I tried to look
for Grabe and his pal
they had disappeared.
They must've taken off
to the hills on foot.
- So where are we now?
- [Crow] Ooh, think about
it later, you're in the lab.
- Except that we do know that
Grabe has been hanging out
at Al's cafe.
- They'll probably never
show up there again.
- But I might find somebody
around there who knows them.
Anyway I'm going
to give it a try.
- [Joel] That's his desk gun.
It's just a spare.
Feels good though.
- [Crow] Al's cafes, serving
the underworlds since 1923.
- Sure, I have seen
him around here.
Talked to him a few times but,
I don't know anything about him.
- What'd you talk to him about?
- Well, I'm a mechanic
and the last time they
asked me to do some work
on a truck motor for him,
I couldn't handle it John
so yesterday I was.
I told him to try Benson's
over on the South side of town,
but I don't know whether they
ever went over there or not.
- I'll check up on that.
Do you know Benson's address?
- Sun Central,
between 14th and 15th,
South side of the street,
- [Joel] But I don't
know his address.
- Good, thanks.
- I'll let you know if
they ever turn up here
again Mr. Cody.
- Good.
See you later.
- [Crow] Boy I hate that guy.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Meanwhile,
back at the casino,
the Keno game raged on.
- [Joel] Ever kissed a dog?
I mean like right on the mouth.
- Crog, calling ready.
- [Crow] Bill, pick
up line one please.
It's your wife Mr. Radick.
- Come in Crog.
- We have the new ray
gun ready to mount
in a well camouflage
truck your excellency.
- And I prepared to
renew our campaign.
- [Tom] And our contracts.
- What are your
first objectives?
- Since the authorities
here learned
of your planned
invasion from the moon,
there have been heavy troop
movements in this area.
We plan to concentrate on
destroying troop trains.
- Very well, work
as fast as possible.
We must have earth's defenses
completely disorganized
before we start our
invasion from the moon.
- Yes your excellency.
- [Joel] Yes your excellency.
Get a bomb, hire some
thugs, get new thugs.
I'm beginning not to believe
this world conquer thing anyway.
- Is everything ready?
- Yes.
We can pick up the
truck and get going.
- Here are the timetables.
The map with points
of attack indicated.
Cover as many of them
as you can today.
- [Crow] And then knock
off for a light lunch,
you guys have been working hard.
- No, I don't remember anyone
answering that description.
But of course we've run a
lot of jobs through here
and I don't know
all the drivers.
- How about these trucks
that are in here now?
- Well, this one and this one
are a couple of my
regular customers.
That one is a cross country job
that came in last night
for an ignition check.
I didn't see who the driver was.
The night man took care of it.
- Okay if I look it over?
- Sure go ahead.
- [Tom] This little honey?
Oh yeah.
It's a smart little lumber.
I can see you're a man
who knows his trucks.
This one's got all the candy.
Going after moon
man, this is perfect.
It's a real honey.
Yep, real crates and everything.
Hey.
- Get away from that truck.
- Hey what's going on?
- Frisk him.
Stay out of this
or you'll get hurt.
- Now look I don't want
any trouble in here.
- [Joel] So I'm just going
to hit you with this crowbar.
- [Crow] Hey Joel,
do mechanics fight better
than scientists do?
- [Joel] Well, they
often have heavy wrenches
in their hands, so
they do a lot better.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Nobody touches
my snap and tools.
Cool.
- [Crow] Hey.
- Just a little thing I made.
I knew we'd use him sometime.
- Oh.
- [Joel] Pretty neat, huh?
- [Crow] Hey, that
guy wrenched his back.
- [Joel] He really
socketed that guy.
- [Crow] (laughing)
He's hammered.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Oh, he
bench pressed him.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Oh look,
he's getting tired.
- [Tom] What a retread.
- [Crow] It's the vice squad.
- [Joel] It's John
Cleese you bustard.
- Let's roll.
(dramatic music)
(car door slams)
- [Crow] Well at least he's
getting used to being beat up.
- [Joel] He's not even hurt.
They must've been using
earth tools or something.
Not even scratch.
♪ Under rules of fun to wear ♪
- A truck load of radios--
♪ And I couldn't fly
from here to there ♪
- I'm sure they're planning
on hiding something inside.
- Probably a ray gun.
- That's what I'm afraid of.
They'll probably start
blasting again anytime now.
I've sent Ted out to the airport
to stand by on a plane
with some light bombs.
- [Crow] He hasn't been
able to lift heavy bombs
since his hernia.
- I'll fly out and try
to locate that truck,
then radio Ted to bomb it.
(phone rings)
Cody laboratory.
- [Tom] Mr. Cody I'm so upset.
They just blasted a troop train
on the Eastern Carson Valley.
I'm here all by myself
and I don't know what
to do please help.
- They just blasted troop train
on the East end
of Carson Valley.
Radio Ted to take off
and I'll find (mumbling)
and fly around out there.
I'll contact him as soon
as I spot the truck.
- Right away.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Hello Dominos.
- Calling Ted Richards.
Calling Ted Richards.
(dramatic music)
(mumbling)
- [Tom] Fly.
- [Joel] Boy, he's
got a nasty tailwind.
- [Crow] It must've
been something he ate.
- [Joel] Shouldn't they take
off before they cropped us.
(mumbling)
- [Crow] Fly that plane Ted.
Get the girl Ted.
Oh, I'm gonna show
him something.
(wind whooshing)
- Calling Ted Richards.
(plane roaring)
Calling Ted Richards.
- Who is it?
Come in.
- [Joel] What do you think Dolt?
- He's going along a dirt road
just East of the
end of the valley.
- I'll be right with you.
- [Cody] Okay.
I'll keep them in
sight you show up.
- [Tom] Does Cody
normally travel
with a full radio pack on.
- [Crow] It's his Radio flyer.
- Flying the harm outfit.
- Hey UPS, Cody must be
tracing a package or something.
- [Crow] Now, this
is the third time
I've done this camera flash
distraction scene, so listen up.
- Cody is after us again.
- We'll stop him, use the rifle.
- [Tom] That should stop him.
(dramatic music)
Pull.
- Oh, missed him, drift left.
(air whooshing)
- [Joel] They got homicide
doors on that thing.
- Did you get him?
- No but I scared him off.
- So they'll fly back and
tell the cops who we are?
- So what?
By the time they get out of
here, we'll be long gone.
(air whooshing)
- Ted.
Ted.
- [Crow] Who is it?
- [Joel] It's me.
It's always going to be me.
Whoever calls you it's me.
(air whooshing)
Let me get that
that door for you.
Yeah.
Yeah, just put that
stuff in the back.
I kind of live in
my plane you know.
If you want to put the
seat back, go ahead.
Just make yourself comfortable.
- What ends?
- Their track is just ahead.
Fly over that dirt road.
- Okay, where are the bombs?
- Right there.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Could you guys
have found a smaller bomb?
What are the odds
of a moving plane,
hitting a moving target
with a moving bomb
that looks like a pineapple.
- [Joel] Oh great double Cody.
Do you have a license
to kill now Mr. Cody?
(bomb blasts)
- What was that?
- [Joel] Oh, just an
exploding dip in the road.
- There is a plane up there,
he must have bombed us.
And it looks like he's
coming back for another try.
- We'll give it a
blast with our ray gun.
- That was pretty close.
We'll drop down a
little lower next time.
- [Joel] This time
use a water balloon.
That will really scare them.
- Hold it up right there.
- [Crow] Okay, let's see.
Bathroom stuff, books,
knickknacks, kid's room.
Hey, where's that
ray gun any way?
Haha!
(plane roaring)
- Hey, they stopped.
- Looks like they
are having glance.
Dive on it quick.
- [Joel] But stay
in the plane Ted.
(plane roaring)
- Hurry up, he's
diving on us again.
(ray gun blasting)
- [Crow] Little blast
from the chevy horn.
- You missed.
- They're too quick.
Turn the track around, I'll
get another another shot on it.
- Right on it.
(plane roaring)
- [Crow] Well, they missed
but how are we going to
get a cliffhanging ending
for this episode?
- You know, my flying helmet's
really hard on my scalp, Ted.
How do you keep yours so
smooth and young looking
besides using shellac
all that time?
(plane roaring)
(ray gun blast)
- [Tom] Well, that's the end.
Next week a new
character for sure.
There's no way you could
get a guy out of that.
(upbeat music)
(dramatic music)
♪ You are watching
Commando Cody ♪
♪ We got new character
character from Republic ♪
♪ He gets in
trouble every week ♪
♪ But he's saved by editing ♪
♪ Just a tweak of the nipples
sends him on his way ♪
♪ A pumpkin head and a rocket
pack he'll save the day ♪
♪ His laboratory
is a boxing ring ♪
♪ When bad guys
come to mix it up ♪
♪ Someday always gets kidnapped
and Cody has to fix it up ♪
♪ He drinks tea at Al's cafe ♪
♪ And flies along on wires ♪
♪ He beats up crooks
and flies with hooks ♪
♪ And puts off floor is fire ♪
♪ Bad Guys be ware
Cody is there ♪
♪ You'll like his hair ♪
♪ It's under his helmet ♪
♪ 'Cause we couldn't
think of a good rhyme ♪
♪ And that's the end of the
Commando Cody theme song ♪
So sit right back and
with a wheel of granite
and watch Chapter
Eight, The Enemy Planet.
(laughing)
- [Tom] Very nice.
- [Joel] On May 17th,
at the eighth superior court
of California, Los Angeles
Graber and his goon
Daly were sentenced
to three consecutive
five-year sentences
at the actor's correctional
facility in Chino.
Daly went on to win the
1989 True Chicago (mumbles).
- You missed.
- They went too quick.
Turn the track around I'll
get another shot at it.
- [Crow] Why don't they
just turn that gun around?
- [Joel] 'Cause it's through,
right through the back
of the truck Crow.
- [Tom] And it's a rented truck.
- [Crow] Yeah, but it's
on a Graber's card.
- [Joel] Yeah, but
he stole that card.
- [Tom] But he's a thief,
he's supposed to steal cards.
- [Crow] Yeah but the
card is the ace of clubs.
- [Joel] No it's the
player's club card.
He rented the truck and
got two free hotel nights
at resorts in the
National Atlantic city,
and as a complimentary
continental breakfast.
- [Tom] Atlantic city!
Atlantic city, slowly I turn.
- [Crow] Oh, Stop it.
- [Tom] Step by step.
- [Crow] vStop it.
They blew up the plane.
- [Tom] That's okay, it was
a rented plane and they--
- [Joel] Okay, stop it.
- [Crow] Truck.
- [Joel] Here he comes.
- [Tom] Wow, incoming.
- [Crow] Wow.
- [Joel] That was a close one.
Meanwhile, back at the Cody
Institute for deceptive editing.
- System of defense
against our (mumbling)
- It's Practically impossible
unless we build ray
guns of our own.
- [Joel] Did you look at
the skull on that guy!
He looks like my dead
uncle uncle Phil, now.
- [Tom] Do you know how much
he charges to haunt a house?
- You think you can do it?
- I'm not sure, but
it's worth trying.
Anything is better than
sitting here like tin ducks
in a shooting gallery.
- I highly agree.
If you're willing
to make the attempt,
you can certainly
have permission.
How soon can you start?
- Right away.
The rocket ship is
all fueled and ready.
Joan, call--
- [Crow] The rocket ship?
We are going back to
the moon it sound like.
- [Joel] Terrific.
- I want to get started
before there's any chance
of the news leaking out.
So Reddick will be laying
for us when we get there.
- [Joel] Watch the
scene everybody, whoops.
- [Crow] Scarecrow, I think
I'll miss you most of all.
- Hope this trip is as
easy as your last one.
- Thanks.
It should be.
- [Tom] Since we're
using the same footage.
- Goodbye.
- Goodbye sir.
- [Joel] You know, they should
invest in the control tower.
- Hurry folks, here we go again.
- All right.
All set.
Any time now.
(dramatic music)
- Safety belt persons.
- [Crow] No, it's not a law yet.
- Fire power jet.
- [Tom] Oh wonderful!
- Fire main jets.
- [Crow] Fire up all the jets.
Get the Asmens back on contract.
- [Joel] This thing's
loaded with candy.
Watch what I can do with it.
(air whooshing)
You know I could
get used to this.
- [Tom] Yes, yes.
- [Joel] Cruising around
in a big jet, lots of beer.
- We're 12 feet high.
Set a course for the moon.
- [Tom] Which moon?
- [Crow] Take a left at
L2, you can't miss it.
Dave's van is parked out front.
- [Joel] Let me show you
what this baby can do.
You guys ever seen
a barrel roll?
(Joel laughs)
- [Crow] Yikes.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] That's it.
If I'd have brought
that straight edge,
we'd make it to the
moon at half the time.
- [Joel] Here, use
my forehead's Phill.
- We're just about here.
We ought be down in
another two hours.
(jet roaring)
- [Tom] I'm really,
really hungry.
Everyone looked
for the Stuckey's.
- I can see the city now.
We don't wanna get too close
to the spring West (mumbling)
- Okay.
(jet roaring)
- [Crow] I see a
thousand points of light,
it looks like Cleveland.
- I'll take her down.
- [Tom] We are now
approaching the moon.
Please place your office
chairs to the upright position.
The temperature on the
moon is a balmy 70 degrees.
Enjoy your stay.
- All right settle her down.
- [Joel] It kinda looks
like the upper Dells.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Tom] Wisconsin is a
beautiful place to be.
- You're sure you don't
want me to go alone?
- No, not this time.
This is just a scouting
trip to try to find
where they keep the little Mary.
- How do you expect to do that?
- Well if I'm lucky,
I'll be able to capture
one of the moon men
and get some
information out of him.
- [Crow] Well, bundle up honey.
It's cold out there.
- [Tom] Oh, radishes!
- [Joel] Good morning,
where's my paper?
Where's our shrubs?
Oh, I'm on the moon,
how silly of me.
Space travel.
And away.
(air whooshing)
So sunny on the moon today.
- [Joel] I'm just standing on
this hill and looking around.
Oh, there I am.
(Crow mumbles)
- [Crow] Give me
that gun, it's mine.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Oh, it's that
old sea hunt routine.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] (mumbles), what are
you trying to do, kill me?
- Do you want me to cut
off your hair again?
- No.
No.
- Where is the lunarian stored?
- I will tell you.
- Think I'll pass.
- Sure you'll pass all right.
- [Joel] Look they are forcing
him to eat Jones cooking.
- He wasn't in any
position to lie very well.
- No he was just getting his
free continental breakfast.
- I think they are one of the
men who got the lunarian--
- [Crow] I can't believe we're
trying to annihilate you.
This is delicious.
Hey pass the jam, will you?
- It's a little after
nine, I'll go right in.
You find a place to hide and
watch for me to come out.
- Okay.
- Cheesy, got rights through
their rigid security system.
I can't believe that.
(soft music)
- About time you got here.
- I was delayed.
- [Tom] I'm a phony, you know.
(soft music)
- [Crow] Oh, that's right,
the sauna closes after 10.
Well, I'll have to use my
my after-hours passkey.
(door creaks)
- [Joel] Ooh right,
I found my Nintendo.
I'm gonna play
Super Mario Brothers
and everything is gonna
be so great, oh Ted.
(door creaking)
- [Crow] Oh, I'm not
sorry for that one.
That felt wonderful.
(Crow coughs)
Oh, I shouldn't do
that in a pressure suit
(Crow coughs)
- You got it.
- Yes.
It's so heavy it's
going to take us a week
to log it back to the ship.
- Get outside, quick.
- [Crow] These moon men
have used this for plywood,
we haven't even dreamed of yet.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] You wait in the car,
I'm gonna go see
if Judy is ready.
(dramatic music)
- Come on.
- [Joel] Judy, I'm down at
the lobby, can you buzz me up?
We got dad's car.
(dramatic music)
Well Kesa Mou said no curfew.
This is going to be the
best road trip ever.
- [Crow] Here's the
lesson for you teens.
Always lock up
and take the keys.
Don't let a good boy go bad.
- Very well.
- [Crow] Ooh dad's
going to be torqued.
I gotta make up a story.
I Wandered to the far
side, yeah that's it.
- Somebody stole my car,
send another one quickly.
- [Joel] Listen, I'm not
gonna bail you out of trouble
every time you lose a car.
Someday I'm not gonna
be there for you.
Yeah.
- How the hill pressure?
- It seems okay.
- [Joel] This is so great.
- [Tom] What those
dupe boys didn't know
is that boss Hog had
stolen the general lead.
(Ted mumbling)
- There he is.
That's right for an near miss.
That might stop him.
- What was that?
- A ray gun blast.
See what's behind us.
- [Joel] I think it's a ray gun.
[Crow] Oh, it's just some car.
That must be, they
want to pass us.
- There is another
car chasing us.
We better use our gun.
- We'll have to turn
around to do it.
There is a bunch rocks that
will give us some shelter.
We'll wait until we get there.
(dramatic music)
- It's heading for some
rocks, we'll have to stop.
(ray gunblast)
- [Joel] Oh, it's the Das
Boot theme all over again.
(mumbling)
- We're stuck.
How say we are?
- Pressure is down to nothing.
I can fix this if I have time.
- [Tom] I took moon
mechanics in high school.
- Stop behind the rock.
But I think I can blast it.
(ray gun blasting)
- [Joel] By this time my
lungs were aching for air.
- [Crow] You hit the helium.
- [Tom] Help me, help me.
Oh no.
(dramatic music)
(doors closing)
Okay Ted, stop here.
I'm gonna hover here for a
moment and survey the landscape.
Okay, now I think I'm gonna
fly over to that window
and look for all those rotten
radar men from the moon.
Are you done yet?
No, I'm not done yet.
Okay, let's do a fly by
at that nudist colony.
Swinging into high
Jedi, I feel the need,
the need for speed.
Come on, Servo.
Who?
I mean Commando Servo.
I think Crow wants
to talk to us.
You're a good little helper Ted.
Let's go, come on.
- Hey, you guy,
I mean earth man.
I want you to take an atomic
bomb the size of a pineapple,
strap it to a Piper Cub and
then crash into Mount Vesuvius.
Then on your way back,
swing by Al's and pick
me up a Swiss cheese
on a college of roll.
I can't get into this.
Joel, I wanna be commander
Cody for a while.
- Ted, who is that
squeaky little worm
in the caftan down there?
- It's Crog and he wants
to wear your costume.
- Does he have any idea
who he is dealing with?
I couldn't...
- Yeah, you're Servo out
when Joel's holding you up.
- Pay no attention to
the man holding me up.
Take me down to
Ted, I'm on a roll.
- Oh come on Servo,
don't be such a baby.
- Alright, Crow, the jig is up.
- Put on the cheese pistol
and fight me like a man.
- I'll jam it in your
centuri bubble head.
Come on, give me that cut.
Lets go moon man, let's gone.
- Saved my commercial sign.
- You're lucky my chick's here.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Fly me in Ted.
- [Joel] No, next time Crow
gets to be Commando Cody.
- [Crow] Did you hear that?
He said I could do it.
- [Tom] Commando
Crow will never work.
You're too much of a pansy.
- [Crow] That's it.
That's it.
I don't know what
it is, but it's it.
- [Joel] Robert Heinlein.
- Hey, get me fellows,
I'm playing the violin.
- [Crow] Jerome Pycha jr.
cousin of Jerome Elite.
Kind of a typist joke.
- [Joel] Miniatures by Jacque...
What do they have
miniatures for?
- [Crow] They used a
lot of Hummel figurines
in the space sequences.
(space music)
- [Tom] Taldmage farm remembers.
- [Joel] In 1948,
the secretary of defense
proposed that the United States
build a space station as a
military guardian of the sky.
By 1954 atom bombs and
Inter-continental rockets
made it a necessity.
1963, the Beatles first
appeared on Ed Sullivan.
1966, the first orbital flight
was made by Colonel Briteis.
By 1970, the space
station had been built
and free men were
reaching the moon.
1977, hot pants became
the height of fashion.
While this was going on,
the enemies of
freedom were not idle.
They were working to
destroy the space station.
- Sector number
12 come in please.
- Sector number 12.
- [Tom] Inspector 12,
he checked my underwear.
- [Crow] Hey, who hasn't?
- Sector number
13, come in please.
- Sector number 13, in.
- Sector number
13 come in please.
Sector number 13 come in please.
- Sector number 13 in.
- [Tom] We want to
recall your underwear.
- Mr. Untrey , we are
all ready for you sir.
- [Joel] Untrey round three.
Hey it's Bob Newhart.
- [Crow] No, it's Bob Hope.
- [Tom] It's Tony and Muldoon.
(Crow barks)
- [Joell] He's gonna get fired.
- [Tom] Look at that, the
fondue set to the future.
- [Crow] Haha, look
at the little tie,
they must've got into
a tie cutting gag.
- Randry here.
- [Joel] Joel here.
- [Tom] Servo here
- [Crow] Crow here.
- [Joel] Joel here.
- [Tom] Servo here.
- [Crow] Crow here.
- I've called you
15 sectional chiefs
to this radio rendezvous.
To brief you on the situation
regarding project A.
We've tried for two years,
to get an agent on
that space station.
But due to impregnable
security precautions,
we have been unable to do so.
- [Crow] Sorry I
blew up like that.
- I have orders from
the minister himself,
that we must not
fail in destroying
this perpetually
menacing eye in the sky,
and it must be done
within two months
- [Joel] Or I'll
be really steamed.
- Therefore I must
have information
on every person who might be
sent to that space station.
I have 300 operatives
with typed resemble all leading
scientists in the field.
- [Joel] And you know
how expensive that is.
- Due do money or family
or some other reason,
these people are under
our absolute control.
Your job will be
to use every man.
- [Crow] Not us.
- Under absolute surveillance.
And so far as possible to
monitor everything they say
and do.
- [Crow] Except the stupid
stuff, the knock knock jokes.
- Lisesmic will transmit to
you the names and addresses
of those people
we wish followed.
- [Tom] Anderson, Andy,
Adams, Al, Ann, Adam.
- It is a 24 hour job.
- [Joel] But don't kill
yourself getting it done,
it's not worth that.
- [Crow] Oh, that seat's warm.
- Calling the San
Francisco sector.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- Here's a special list
for your attention.
John Adams, Henry Burns.
(phone rings)
Standby.
Yes.
- [Tom] Wow, how futuristic?
- [Crow] Oh, that phone bill
is going to be enormous.
- We have information on
the next man make this trip.
- Yeah I wanted
to find this out.
Just a second, I'll
call Mr. Roundtree.
- [Crow] Roundtree
hey, that chef.
- Important call for you sir.
- [Joel] Oh, I was just mowing
on my own knee, excuse me.
(dramatic music)
Thank you for
warming up the seat.
- Roundtree here.
- Your man for project
A is Dr. Wernher.
Repeat, Dr. Werhner,
W-E-R-N-H-E-R.
- [Joel] What's it spell?
- [Crow] Wernher.
- [Joel] What's it mean?
- [Crow] Deadly.
- Check the files.
See if we have a dr.
Wernher, W-E-R-N-H-E-R.
- [Joel] What's that spell?
- [Crow] Wernher.
- [Joel] What's it's mean.
- [Crow] Deadly.
- Quickly.
- Well, here you are sir.
- You have a double
for him, all right.
He's in San Francisco under
a section chief three.
Jack resemblance,
except for the hair.
- [Tom] It's the
Wernher brothers.
- Oh, that's easy to fix.
- [Joel] Send me
some Grecian formula.
- Now here's your
plan of action.
Dr. Wernher is staying at the
central hotel in room 524.
I'll have a set of photographs
to you within 15 minutes.
- [Tom] It's the
future, we can do that.
- Surround the hotel with
a coating of operatives.
- Get a room as close
to them as possible,
preferably next door.
- [Crow] That's as
close as possible.
- I will be there
within two hours
to take charge of
the operation myself.
(upbeat music)
(door slams)
- [Joel] They'll
never notice this bag
the size of an nipple lady.
- Ready here.
Testing one, two, three, four.
(door slams)
- All right Sam,
we'll be able to hear
everything that goes on.
- [Joel] We can hear you
right through the door.
- You keep your ear glued to
that receiver until you leave.
- [Crow] Could you
send some solvent
at the end of my shift.
- [Tom] Sure.
- Mr. Rountree, Dr.
Wernher just came in.
(phone rings)
- Hello.
- [Green] This is
general Green speaking.
- Oh, yes General.
- [Green] Delighted
to hear it from you.
- I expected that you
would call me, yes.
All arrangements
have been completed
for the circumlunar flight.
- [Joel] In the future all
phones will be invisible.
- [Crow] His hand
is glued to his ear.
- [Tom] He's a hell
of a mime though.
- Yes, sir.
- [Green] You'll
make arrangements
through the local
transportation office.
- Good.
Fine.
Thank you.
- [Joel] Supper,
great, unbelievable,
couldn't be better.
Loving life, but you know.
Before I go I got--
- Where is that devil?
- [Tom] He's shooting
a double miniere.
- Well, I'm I be
living any moment.
- He'll be here shortly.
His plane arrived at the
airport 25 minutes ago.
- [Crow] Sarah,
the glue has set.
- [Joel] Lion shark double.
- Finally.
- Sorry I was detained.
- [Crow] I was doubling
for someone else.
I was double duty.
- Thank you.
- You know your job.
- I know.
- You must destroy
the space station.
According to all my
available information,
there is only two
ways of doing it.
- [Tom] Neither are very good.
- One by getting into the
bottom room of the station
and setting off
one of the bombs.
Two, by taking control
of the moon shift,
which is scheduled to take
and ramming it into the station.
- [Joel] There's a
bonus if you get killed.
- I understand.
- Sam take him into
the dressing room
and match his head
to that photograph.
- Yes sir.
- [Tom] Or match the photo
to the hair, either one.
- Well, how does the hair look?
- [Crow] Like the photograph.
- [Wernher] Yes,
this is Dr. Wernher.
- Yes, Colonel, I've
been waiting for you.
A car in front of the
hotel in 10 minutes.
Good.
I'll be there, sir.
- [Joel] A big official car.
- An official car.
I'll watch for the insignia.
Thank you, sir.
Goodbye.
- He's gonna leave
in 10 minutes.
- Good.
- Desk, Wernher here.
Send a man for my bags please.
Thank you.
- Send for a bellhop.
- [Tom] What luck, I have
to be dressed as a bellhop.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Gorilla
bell boy double.
- Come in.
Oh, you.
Take these two bags here
and I'll take the briefcase.
- [Crow] Uh-oh, he
forgot to say please.
- How did you get
here so quickly?
- [Joel] That's how I
got here so quickly.
- [Tom] (mumbles) lady.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Wow, look at all
this neat stuff he's got.
Wow, great bet he got
this at The Sharper Image.
Hey, I'm keeping that.
- Do I look like him?
- You don't.
We wasted a full year looking
for you for this assignment.
- [Joel] I know that in
your own way that means yes.
- Don't worry, I know my job.
- Your credentials Dr. Wahrner.
- Just a moment.
- [Crow] I'm a
real bell boy, sir.
- Come in.
- You rung sir?
- Yes.
You take those two bags and
I'll take the briefcase.
- [Crow] He forgot
to say, please.
- Do you want a cab sir?
- No, I'm expecting a
car, an official car.
- [Joel] How did you
get here so fast?
- [Joel] Meanwhile, in
Estes Park, Colorado.
- Dr. Wahrner.
- [Crow] I'll be filling in
for your receipts monkey.
- [Joel] I see your
hair plug's took.
- General is waiting
for you, sir.
- Thank you.
- And our doctor will
rush you through security.
This way please.
- Sergeant, bags.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] SPACOM, wood
fill and meat substitute.
- [Crow] We built
this city of SPACOM.
- [Joel] Instead
of rock and roll?
- [Crow] Yap.
- You see Bill ,
according to my calculus,
36 million miles should
be equal to the ratio
of 67 (mumbling).
- [Joel] Cut the crap
doctor, I love you.
- [Tom] Look, it's Dr. Bellow.
- Yes, what is it?
- Dr. Werhner has arrived and
is going through security sir.
- Good.
Tell him I'll meet him for the
briefing as soon as possible.
Say within a half hour.
- [Crow] Within a half hour.
- Well, that's a break.
I was afraid we
would have to cancel
just because one a compounded
civilian was going to be late.
- If you please sir,
I don't really see why we
have to take him at all.
Mackintosh and I
can photograph the back face
of the moon without help.
- A lot of politics
in these things boy.
If we hadn't played
the science angle,
we wouldn't have gotten
the authorization.
- [Crow] Funny how sciece
figures in the space travel.
- This round the moon flight
is a necessarily a step
to the establishment
of a lunar base,
and you know how badly the
country needs that base.
- [Crow] I do but could
you go over it again?
- And I'm mighty pleased
the geo to be the pilot.
I hated to bump you
out of the honor
of making the first
orbital flight Bill but,
well it just had to be Breteis.
You know our reasons.
- Well that's year passed
and I'm done with it sir.
- Breteis is a good pilot.
- I'd be the first to admit it.
- You used to like
Breteis, right?
- Frankly Sir,
Captain Breteis was
a nice kid but...
Well Colonel Breteis is
a little hard to swallow.
- Lindenberg got promoted from
captain to colonel for less.
The precedent is simply follow
the established precedent.
- I suppose so sir.
Anyhow, this makes up for it.
Being the first man
to fly around the moon
is all any pilot can ask for.
- [Joel] Your a
donut rapper sir.
- [Tom] Thank you Private Pilot.
- [Crow] This is from Bismarck.
- [Joel] I hate communiques
in Abu Dhabi, let's see that.
Round moon, flight period,
briteis reporting to SPACOM
soon at, period, this change.
- [Crow] Sounds like
they're still typing it.
- Notify me immediately
on cradle Briteis arrival
and cut the audits accordingly.
- Yes, sir.
- [Tom] Your donut rapper sir.
- Oh no sir, not again.
They can't do this sir.
- Sit down Bill,
and take it easy.
- You saw where those
orders originated.
- [Bill] Yes, sir but I--
- I said sit down
Bill and take it easy.
- [Crow] Sitting sir.
Taking it easy sir.
- Here have a smoke.
- [Crow] Smoking...
Oh, excuse me sir.
- [Bob] Sir there were
50 reporters outside
with about six truck
loads of cameras.
They told me Breteis
is going to--
- Yes I know Bob.
Route them through
PRO and a security
and set up the briefing room.
- [Crow] Then turn
a hose on them.
- We'll have to actually get
this through before blast off.
- Oh Bill.
- Yes, sir.
- I'm sending you as co-pilot.
- What?
No sir.
I mean, well excuse me sir but,
if it's all the same to you
leave Macintosh as co-pilot.
- [Joel] He's a good apple.
- I just assumed
I'll have the honor.
Besides, well it wouldn't
be fair to Macintosh.
- It's not a matter
of being fair.
This isn't some school boy game.
This trip has got
to be successful.
Besides I have more
confidence in you
than I have a
Macintosh, or Breteis.
But if it were any
of the pilots sir.
- Of course I could go
through the joint chiefs
to the president,
make a squat but,
that would mean
postponing the flight.
- [Crow] That would
mean graveling
and you know how
I hate to do that.
- I'll do it.
- Good boy.
- Thanks Bill.
- [Joel] Have a biscuit Bill.
- [Tom] No biscuits, make me--
(phone rings)
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
- Colonel Breties is here sir.
- Send the Colonel in.
- Poly Prattles is
with the Colonel sir.
- What!
- [Crow] Send Polly
Prattles to Pittsburgh.
Pittsburgh is perfect for
the prissy press pre-Madonna
with prestel (mumbles) pants.
- [Joel] Beauty!
- Colonel Breteis,
reporting as ordered sir.
- [Crow] And the beast.
- My dear general.
- [Joel] She enters
the scene like a float.
- You know, I told
the president,
I was so delighted
(mumbling) to see you again.
- [Crow] Does the phrase
drop anchor mean anything?
- Well thank you Ms. Prattle,
but we are have a press
conference in a few minutes.
- Oh but General,
I hoped you might
give me an exclusive.
- I'm very sorry Ms. Prattles,
it's policy you know.
- The president told Polly
she could interview us.
- What?
Oh very well Ms. Prattles,
I'll give you a 15 minutes here
before the meeting in the
briefing room, will that do?
- Just lovely.
But in the meantime--
- We're all set up for
the press conference
and TV broadcast sir.
- Well Thanks Charlie.
Oh will you take Ms.
Prattles and major Moore
for a cup of coffee
and bring them back here
in about 20 minutes?
I have a few classified matters
to discuss with the colonel,
highly classified.
- [Crow] Spanking time!
- Colonel, I'm sending major
Moore as your co-pilot.
- Bill Moore!
Oh no general you can't.
- And why not?
- The big lug hates me.
He's jealous of me.
No, you'll have to
pick someone else.
- Now you listen to me Breteis.
- Breteis if you please.
- Shut up Breteis
and listen to me.
Major Moore is the best pilot
we have better than you are.
- But I don't
understand why you--
- Pipe down.
- [Joel] Then be quiet.
- If he'd weighed 90
pounds instead of 180--
- [Crow] Then he'd
be my prom date.
- And you'd still be a captain.
But you got the orbital flight.
You got the ticker tape
arrays and all the rest.
- [Crow] You got to
be on your own room,
the princess' phone, the
TV whenever you wanted it.
- No I won't.
- One, colonels don't
say no to generals.
Two, you're not a super
woman, you are a spoiled brat.
Three, any more guts out of you
and I'll turn you over
my knee and spank you.
- If you do, I'll shout
the whole place down.
- I might add that this
room is soundproof.
- You wouldn't dare.
- You wanna to try me.
- [Joel] I spanked your
co-pilot, didn't I?
- No sir.
- [Joel] Then we'd
better get out here--
- All right.
- [Tom] Spanking
really is protocol
in the upper echelons of NASA.
- Let's talk about
this flight, shall we?
(upbeat music)
- [Joel] As illustrated in
this film, thank you Cambot,
the tire of the future
will be cut short
to eliminate the age
old warning question,
Is it appropriate to tuck
my tie into my pants?
In the future it won't
even be an option.
In fact,
there'll be no room in the
future for fashion blunder
when the short guy, a
Gogo tie swings into high.
But what other roads will a tie
take in days of future past?
To start things off, Tom Servo,
who we call Cheeky, is
sporting the Hex Field body tie
from the year 4,000.
That's right, whether
you're inside, outside,
or upside down, the Hex
Field body tie fits and fits.
Very nice Tom, thank you.
- Don't talk to me.
I'm a high fashion
model from the future.
- Sorry Tom.
I'm wearing the anti-gravitie.
This tie is a brainchild of
the defective fashion jackals
direct to use store.
It implies to the
travel conscious that
you're no stranger
to anti-gravity space travel.
Pop up, sleeves are optional.
Crow from the planet
Julio Coriocan,
rages on into the year 9,000
with a tie that acknowledges
men will always dribble.
- Oops.
Uh-oh.
It senses the soup on your lips,
reaches up and
dabs the soup away.
And now our own
Tom servo is back
just out of the dressing
room I might add
in the nick of time with
the ultimate tie designed
for our friends from the church
of the future machismo irony.
They guarantee this
will stay stylish
for millennia to come.
This tie is from the warp
burning plastic collection,
again from those fashion
drones on module five.
This tie automatically lengthens
to ever changing tides
and trends of fashion.
(loud beeping)
- Ooh we got a movie signs,
let's cheese and let's go.
(doors creaking)
- A rocket flight from the
earth directly to the moon--
- [Joel] I thought that
tie thing was funny,
I don't know about you.
- But now that we have a
satellite station in space,
revolving around the earth,
a satellite do I might add,
directly to the heroic
first orbital flight
by Colonel Breteis,
four years ago.
Now that we have
a space station--
- [In unison] Or a Frisbee.
It is at last possible
to send a ship--
- [In unison] Or batteries.
- All the way around the moon.
- [In unison] Or
a playground ball.
- On this trip, Dr. Wahrner
will photograph the back face--
- [In unison] Or double.
- The ship will then return
to the space station.
- [In unison] Or a Frisbee.
- I'm so glad--
- [In unison] Or a large barge.
- And so will all readers be,
but General, what's the
purpose of all this?
- What do you mean Ms. Prettle?
- Well, my editor,
an old bag nothing
ever see suits him.
Well, he says this whole
thing is boondoggle.
Just another way of
wasting tax money.
Now what am I to tell him?
(Crow mumbling)
- This round of the moon
flight is a necessary step
before establishing
a base on the moon.
It's a survey flight.
- Maybe someday the statesman--
- [Joel] He's so military,
I thought he gives
good spankings.
- It's so fine but
in the meantime,
if there is going to
be a base on the moon
and there will be--
- [Tom] I wanted
to be first place.
- [Joel] I'm not even
supposed to be here.
- Ma'am, the most important
thing in the world to me
is the military security
of the United States.
- [Crow] And my dog Flappy.
- And I'm not in the least bit
apologetic for my attitude.
- I wonder general,
could you tell me something
about this wonderful
space station.
- [Joel] I'll help you
with the cue cards.
- That will be very
interesting general.
- Well, I can give
you a rough idea.
The station is a titanium
hole, with steel bracing,
350 feet in diameter.
It rotates completely
around the earth
in a trans-polar orbit,
about 10 times a day.
At present the station is
in a state of free fall.
- Free fall, could you explain
that a little bit more.
- Off course, when we
speak to free fall,
we simply mean that the
station and everything in it,
are moving around the earth
at a speed which is
great enough so that
it cannot fall toward the earth,
but it is also
moving at the speed,
which is not great enough
in order to enable it
to go out into space.
Therefore,
the forces of gravity and
speed are now in balance.
(Joel sighs)
- [Joel] That was very good.
Yeah.
Nothing in the station
has any weight.
- No, wait, what
a wonderful idea!
You mean if I went I
wouldn't wear anything.
- Nothing at all.
As a matter of fact,
you'd have to wear magnetic
shoes to keep you on the floor.
- [Crow] Well, I have a
pink out of those at home.
- I wondered general,
could I arrange to go
there, to the space station?
- Well, hardly Ms. Prettles.
- [Joel] There's
the little problem
of escape philosophy ma'am.
- It's about $300 a pound to
send anything to the station.
And consequently,
our personnel almost always
less than 160 pounds.
- [Joel] You're over
by a metric tone.
- It is so lovely to
weigh nothing at all.
(laughing)
- I've heard of
the H bomb General.
Isn't it dangerous living
and working so near to it.
- I'm very sorry doctor,
but that's a highly
classified subject.
- [Crow] A simple yes
or no would do dickweed.
- [Joel] Isn't she something?
- [Crow] Yeah and the
girl ain't bad either.
- General Green, your rocket
ship number three editor,
ready for takeoff
to space station.
- [Joel] No diving
or splashing please.
And no running on the deck.
- Happy landing, sir.
- Colonel Breteis,
your ship is zero.
Check off list completed.
- Do you need any help?
- No thank you Major,
I'm perfectly capable of
getting into the rocket myself
- [Joel] Well all right,
Ms. Gloria Steinem.
- [Tom] That's Miss
Glorious Steinem.
- [Joel] Aright yeah.
- [Tom] Hey, and
there's only one bunk.
- May I strap you in colonel.
- No, thank you major.
Are your ship to ship
and ship to blockhouse
frequencies operating?
- Incoming only colonel.
- Orders are to keep
the channels clear
until the Canada blast off.
- Canada to blockhouse,
request permission
to start pumps.
- [Crow] Sorry yeah,
but Canada is dry.
- Request permission
to blast off.
- Permission granted.
- [Crow] Hey Canada,
take off your hoses.
- [Joel] Yeah our subject
today is space launches.
So we're gonna have a takeoff.
Hey, you get it?
You know it's kinda like a
rocket it's going to take off
and then they say
take off on that bit.
- [Crow] Look at that take off.
- [Joel] Well good
day to you then.
(rocket flying)
- You may start blast
off procedure captain.
- Thank you colonel.
- Mexico to blockhouse,
request permission
to start pumps.
- Permission granted.
- Mexico to blockhouse.
- [Crow] Make a
run for the border.
- Blockhouse to Mexico,
clearance granted.
You are minus 10 seconds.
Nine,
eight.
- [Tom] Three.
- Seven.
- [Tom] 13.
- Six.
- [Joel] nine.
- Five.
[Tom] 128.
- Four.
- [Tom] 33.
- 1,000,005.
- Two, one.
- [Joel] Don't blow
it, it's a big trunk.
Buddy absence's happy.
(people yelling)
- [Tom] She's
absolutely ballistic.
(dramatic music)
- Base control to Mexico.
Prepare to receive line.
- [Tom] It looks like
Deep 13 kind off.
- Turn to lock
free, bring them in.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Welcome to wammo world.
- [Joel] That ought to do it.
- Lock three to Mexico,
you are secured.
You may disembark, over.
- Mexico to lock
three disembarking.
(people barking)
I must report immediately.
See you before you leave.
I'll be with you as
far as weight control.
- [Joel] I don't need
any weight control,
maybe a tummy tuck or something.
- [Tom] This is all muscle.
(dramatic music)
- [Announcer] Simon winds up.
And it's a pitch.
And it's a home
run for Brooklyn.
- Back to business major.
- [Crow] This is the future
when they sold the
Dodgers back to Brooklyn.
- Hope you enjoyed
the trip colonel.
Happy landings Bill.
- Thank you Captain.
- [Joel] Oh, you dropped
your pen, shoe's untied.
(Joel laughs)
I love this.
- [Crow] Hey, don't
cross the split screen.
- [Joel] Art designed
by MC Escher.
- Please be seated.
- Thank you, sir.
- Nice to see you
again colonel, major.
- [Crow] Major.
- [Joel] Colonel.
- [Crow] Doctor.
Captain.
You're in free fall.
- The General's
asked me to brief you
on the conditions of this shoot.
As you know, it's to be
a circumlunar flight.
Colonel Breteis will pilot,
major Moore co-pilot.
Doctor Werhner will do the
photographic and scientific work
as you pass around the
back face of the moon.
- I think we should
attempt a landing sir.
- [Joel] Shut up.
- One step at a time colonel.
There'll be only a 25
second margin of fuel,
open above that calculator that
is necessary for the flight
and resumption of the
orbit for the station.
Therefore, you must
proceed exactly
according to your flight plan.
If you make this one all right,
we may give you a crack
at the first moon landing.
- [Joel] Breteis for 50 points.
- The Magellan is fueled
and ready according to plan.
Check off list completed.
- [Joel] Bill for 20 points.
- You'll burst
off in 37 minutes.
It's yours colonel.
Man Your ship.
- [Crow] Or woman
your ship as it were.
(Crow laughs)
- [Joel] Boy, walking on the
walls must be a big problem.
- [Tom] Speed bump.
(dramatic music)
- Magellan to lock four,
all secure shove off.
- [Tom] Same to you tuts.
- Lock four to Magellan.
Shoving off on count of ten.
- [Crow] The technical
term of shoving off.
- [Breteis] Magellan
to space control.
Check starting
coordinates, over.
- Your coordinates of polaris
83 degrees, 62 minutes,
max's A, regulars 180
degrees, 29 minutes.
max's B, clomohog--
- [Joel] (mumbling).
Radius, meaningless
dribble, over.
- [Tom] Initiate cheesy
effects sequence.
- [Crow] Roger that,
initiating cheesy FX pill.
- [Joel] Look they're using
View-Master technology.
- [Tom] Battery pack
separating from Frisbee.
(dramatic music)
- [Joel] Look the Grand Tetons.
- Swing slowly right
about two degree.
No south, one degree.
Little more down.
Hold it.
- [Tom] Perfect.
(loud beeping)
- [Breteis] Steady.
Hold it.
- [Joel] Handling the Indian
ceremony at the grand Canyon.
- Rocketship Magellan
to space control.
We are now correctly
aligned, over.
- You have 13
seconds to blast off.
Mark,
13,
12,
11,
10,
nine,
eight,
seven,
six,
five
four,
three,
two,
one,
fire.
- [Crow] Wow, free game.
- [Joel] Duracell away
the copper top shuttle.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Bye.
Bon voyage.
- [Joel] Numbers are really
meaningless in a gravitometer.
- [Crow] Initiate
meaningless lights.
- [Tom] And up it goes.
(upbeat music)
- But what is
controlling the ship now?
- As you can see by the
lights and the tape control,
the autopilot is keeping
us on our computer track
with the ship and
its proper attitude.
Ordinarily the rocket jets are
controlled by the autopilot,
but the pilot can
always fire by hand.
Now, if I were to
throw this switch,
I would override
the automatic pilot
and the jets would fire.
- So but, how
would you guide it?
- [Crow] Well, it's broken.
- Well, you don't
exactly steer a rocket
since there's nothing out
there to grab hold of.
You must first turn
it by the flywheels,
and then it is held
steady by the gyroscopes
while you fired the jets.
- Very interesting.
Very interesting indeed.
Thank you very much.
- [Joel] She always gets
to look in the View-Master.
These people are dressed
like camp counselors.
- Like this?
- I can't work now, the
co-pilot board is dead.
- Who?
- I wouldn't touch it though.
- I'm sorry.
- Think nothing of it doctor.
The major doesn't
like for someone else
to play with his toys,
but that's enough now.
I'll give you another
lesson tomorrow.
- [Crow] Get that
lady a sauce or milk
- [Joel] Meow.
- I think we have the
cameras adjusted now
They can run by themselves
for an hour or two.
- But doctor you haven't
set the automatic trip yet.
(Joel laughs)
- [Joel] The
automatic trip, yeah.
It's hard to take anyone in
a flannel skullcap seriously.
- I'll be glad to fix it.
- Oh fine.
And while you're back after,
I think I'll warm up the radio.
We'll be back
inside aboard soon.
Maybe I can find out how
the world series game on.
I suppose you're a Dodger fan.
- [Tom] Do they play (mumbles)?
- I thought you used
to teach in Brooklyn.
- Oh, that's right.
I'll go below.
You see if you can raise earth.
[Joel] If I could
raise the earth,
I wouldn't need to go
into space shoot doult.
- [Crow] Hey, there's no safety
rail on that access hall.
- [Tom] He's not really just
crawling into the septic tank.
- Colonel.
Colonel wake up.
- What is the Bill?
- That guy Werhner, is a phony.
- What!
Explain yourself.
(mumbles)
- I know more about his
cameras than he does.
- I think you're
imagining things.
- [Crow] No Werhner is a weaner.
- I am.
He's supposed to
be from Brooklyn
and he's never even
heard of the Dodgers.
Look, I don't know
what his game is.
Maybe it's sabotage.
- [Bleteis] What's there to--
- [Joel] The spy
comes out of the hole,
runs around the control
panel then goes back down in.
(Bleteis screams)
- [Tom] Oh my God!
- [Joel] It's hands down.
The slap happiest game ever.
- [Tom] I am not an animal.
- [Crow] Got your nose.
- [Joel] While Breteis
relaxes in the chase lounge,
Jim will attempt to
subdue the angry spy.
- [Crow] This is
low impact aerobics.
- [Joel] It's low
impact filmmaking too.
Higher and higher they climb,
to heights they've
never been to before
and it was good.
- [Joel] Got to push a button.
Got to slow down our orbit now.
Up up up.
Got to find way
to get partner
- [Crow] Thank goodness.
- [Tom] Nice tag.
(somber music)
- [Crow] Honey, come here.
Look the spy looks so
cute when he's sleeping.
- [Joel] We better get
outta here come on.
- [Tom] It looks like one
of your prom dates Joel.
- Thanks a lot.
(doors slamming)
- [Joel] It's new.
- [Tom] It's improved.
- [Crow] It's SPACOM.
As seen in the movie
Project Moon Base.
- [Joel] Yes SPACOM.
The miracle home product,
you thought you'd never need.
- [Crow] Part wood,
part industrial resin,
part pasteurized processed
cheese food product.
- [Joel] That valuable
China crack, no problem.
Just a double SPACOM
we'll do the trick.
- [Crow] Try SPACOM
on an onion roll
for a real lunchtime treat.
- [Joel] Takes care of
rust and that old jalopy
and ladies will just
love how SPACOM removes
those nagging liver
spots and (mumbling).
- [Crow] Slice thin and for
a fabulous rose substitute.
- [Joel] Kids will just
have a ball with SPACOM.
- [Crow] Change your
mother into a basketball
and drive out rodents
and other household pets.
- [Joel] Includes SPACOMin your
next oil change to lubricate
and remove diaper rash
while it widens your wash
and melts those pounds away.
- [Crow] Mike
Polynesian cheese devils
with a little marshmallow cream,
a handful of crunchy fire ants
and lots of velvety SPACOM.
- [Joel] Eskimos love the
way SPACOM takes the gum out
of diesel generators.
- [Crow] Mum loves the
way it cleans jewelry.
- [Joel] Dad loves the way
it takes the pain off that
old table in the attic.
- [Crow] And kids just love
it for a snack anytime.
- [Joel] Massage
it into your scalp,
for refreshing change of mind.
- [Crow] Rub it into your chest
and feel the petroleum
vapors go to work.
- [Joel] Not an aerosol,
not a paste and not
available in any store.
- [Crow] It's SPACOM.
And it's available
at this one time,
low, low, everyday
bargain price.
- [Joel] And if you order now,
you'll receive it
no extra charge
a year's supply of SPACOM.
- [Crow] Cuts through this
tomato like it was a tin cans.
- [Joel] Snuffles caps off jars,
bottles and the baby.
And boy does it catch fish.
(upbeat music)
- [Joel] You can tell
they're about to land
'cause the music couldn't
get any lower you know.
- [Tom] The lunar Explorer model
sets down with the
moon surface model.
- [Crow] That's one small
step for special effects.
One giant leap for
our imagination.
- [Joel] That was great.
There was nothing
fake about that one.
- [Crow] Oh, these
shorts are binding.
- [Tom] Like his contract.
- [Joel] Breteis, get
your shoes on honey.
We're at grandpa's.
He might even have a
quarter for you honey.
- We made it, didn't we?
- [Crow] Excuse me, space food,
dehydrated ice cream, you know.
- I guess so.
The pressure is still high.
- [Joel] úCare to tango?
- I feel I muffed it.
What do we do?
- Take it easy.
Come on.
- But you don't understand.
There isn't enough fuel left.
We can't take off.
Sorry to have gone
female on you major.
I didn't mean to take
advantage of you.
- That's all right.
I'm feeling kind
of punchy myself.
- What do you
think we should do?
- You're asking my
advice, officially.
- [Joel] Let's start a life.
You and me and the
double makes three.
- In that case,
I think you better
powder your nose.
- Go soak your head.
- And while you're doing that,
I'm going to get rid of him.
- What are you going
to do with him?
- [Crow] Well, I thought
I dressed him up like us.
That's pretty degrading.
- I quit shoving
through the airlock.
But instead I think I'll the
tie him up in the storeroom.
I got an idea about
him for later on.
- What is it?
- Don't worry.
It'll be rough.
- [Joel] Oh, that one
set off the fire alarm.
- Now we've got more important
things to worry about.
- How much food there is.
How much water, how much air.
- [Tom] How much love.
- And which one runs out first.
- Bill they will rescue us?
Certainly they will.
- Oh, how will they find us?
We've been out of
radio communication
ever since we went
around behind the moon.
- [Joel] She left a
trail of breadcrumbs.
- They probably landed
out of sight of earth.
- We might as well
be on Neptune.
- [Crow] Come on, little fella
you're going to get bed sores.
- [Tom] Slide, please.
- [Joel] This is us
at the grand Canyon.
We got sore on those boroughs.
This is a Glacier National Park.
Little Bobby turned his ankle
and we had to go
back down early.
This is Space Mountain
at Disney World.
You know,
Bobby lost his corn dog
over on the matter of one.
Am I boring you with this stuff?
- [Crow] No, not at all.
Hey, look, I walk in trashcan.
- [Joel] What a way to go!
- Bill what can we do?
- Now first let's
find out where we are.
- Alright.
I'll take the (mumbles).
And as soon as I have a fixture
you can (mumbles)
into to the computer.
- Okay?
(Tom laughs)
- Meanwhile, back
at Frisbeefour.
- What's a Frisbeefour.
- A report from the Mejalan sir.
She is now exactly 14
minutes, 14 seconds overdue.
- Our agent must
have done something.
While they couldn't be
even 40 seconds overdo.
They were in their orbit?
They've been interfered
with them somewhere.
I'll do a continuous radar
surveillance of all their area
in their emerging sector and
keep an operator on that radio
until we hear from them.
- [Joel] I'll stay here
and bark out orders.
- Where are we located?
- Well, according
to my calculations,
we're about 125 miles
past the crater Grimaldi.
- [Crow] We're centrally located
just out the shloss and cutoff.
- My father's position
on which we could beam a signal
to the satellite station.
- [Joel] And two doors down
from the subway sandwich shop.
- Could you possibly
rigger relay boys
to one of those mountain
peaks in that direction.
- I don't know.
- Our oxygen tanks on our space
only carry a four hour supply.
- [Joel] We actually do
a show that has a barn.
- So it wouldn't
be too difficult.
If I could make it.
- Oh Bill you must, you must.
- There's only one
way I can do it.
I'll have to go down and get
Wharner, and take him with me.
- [Crow] TV sets.
- Warhner get up.
We've landed on the moon.
But since we're beyond
radio reach of the earth,
I have to go out
and set up a relay.
- [Joel] Have fun.
- And you're coming with me.
Our lives depend
upon us doing this.
- [Joel] Set up a
relay with two guys,
it doesn't make sense.
It's not worth it.
- It's a gamble whether
or not we'll ever make it.
- [Joel] Bet you
a see note we die.
- Alright.
I'm with you.
I wouldn't have done this
if I had been pushed into.
let's go.
And remember one false
move and you get this.
- [Crow] Wow Cool.
Can I keep it?
- [Joel] Well, your wrist
didn't grow together?
I was wrong.
- [Crow] This is the way
the first lander died.
- Bill is sporting game
light cotton jumper
pleaded at the knees and is
carrying a set of rabbit ears.
Notice the rich styling
on his rabbit ears.
Very futuristic.
While the turncoat,
- Thank you.
- [Joel] Enjoys a
spandex sports suit
fashionable for either
work or sabotage.
- [Tom] From moon flex $150.
- Wish us luck colonel.
- Good luck Bill.
Happy landing.
- [Crow] Didn't
they already land.
- [Joel] Suckers.
(Crow laughs)
- Bill do you read me?
Come in Bill.
- [Joel] Oh, that's where
my old school used to be.
- I'll call you back
in about two hours.
- [Crow] Okay, but
mom's calling later.
So if it's busy, keep trying.
- [Joel] They look like
salt and pepper shakers.
- [Crow] Hey a bah, bah,
I'll give you a nickel
if you scale that cliff.
I'll show you my sore toe.
- [Joel] Cliff
diving on the moon.
- [Crow] Their heads
look like bell jars.
- Come on, be a man.
Get up that rock.
You're one, six year old away.
Come on you woose.
Beat cheeks.
I can't believe what a
spazz you are now come on.
If you don't get your
butt up on that rock
on the count of three.
I'm going to hurt
your insides boy.
That's right.
- [Tom] Night of
a thousand stars.
- [Crow] Wow that ships
only three feet away.
It looks like a model from here.
- Well it is.
- [Joel] Well now at least
we'll be able to get HBO.
- Breteis,
We have established
the relay station
and we're returning
to the ship now.
Our oxygen reserve may not
be enough to carry us back.
If we don't make it,
good luck and God bless you.
- [Crow] I'm sorry, what?
I wasn't listening.
- [Tom] Be very
careful going down.
Those rocks could be
very, very slippery.
- [Joel] Oh, come on.
What could happen?
Were one sixth their own
weight, nothing can--
(Joel groans)
Right in the butt.
- [Tom] Quit fooling
around, down there.
- [Crow] Nice half gainer.
- Oh that's no, I got a drag--
- [Tom] He's a half traitor now.
- [Joel] Half traitor?
- Bill, come in Bill.
- [Crow] What?
Sleeping on the job again huh!
- [Joel] Looks like we got
another fish tank for the ship.
Oh I hate when that
happens poor guy.
- [Crow] By this time,
my lungs were aching for air.
- [Joel] Isn't that her
lying from see hunt.
- [Crow] Yeah.
- [Joel] Get back to where
you once belonged Jojo.
- [Tom] I didn't
mean to hurt anybody.
We were just playing, mom said
sometimes I play too rough.
I'm probably a lot bigger
than the other kids are.
I would just go for an off
and now I guess he's dead.
I was playing well and it
wasn't really my fault.
I feels like such a jerk.
I never really killed
anybody before.
I don't know.
I just got to learn to be
around with the other kids.
I spent a lot of time
with my books in my room.
Well, I don't know.
I'm just no good.
I don't even deserve
to eat supper tonight.
- Breteis.
- I'm just barely
able to make it.
- [Tom] This is no time
to make dust angels.
Get up.
Put down the hoist module.
- [Crow] Hey, pretend
your legs don't work.
That's cool.
It's fun.
- Hi guys?
I'm so cold.
- [Joel] Well Your
not that bad of a guy.
You got your warm moments.
(somber music)
- [Tom] In the center ring for
your pleasure and excitement.
The only area like
the other moon.
Come on, come on.
- [Crow] It's a
GI Joe action set.
Comes with moon man,
space pot and
detachable retners.
- [Joel] Head and
legs sold separately.
- [Crow] By Blammo.
- Magellan display comm.
Comm input.
- [Joel] W-M-O-N-T-V has
canceled its broadcast day.
We will resume
programming at 7:00 AM,
and now our National Anthem.
- [Breteis] Magellan
display comm.
Come in please.
- Did you make it work?
- I'm afraid not Bill.
I have been trying for five
hours and nothing is happening.
- [Maybe we should haven't
pointed that antenna towards
- Should it be?
- Yes.
I hooked our emergency relay
to tie in with the
Fort television model.
Press number three
on your board.
- [Crow] No, not
that channel three.
- Space come to
Magellan, we read you.
- If should have came to
consciousness a lot sooner
it would have saved
us a lot of trouble.
- Good.
SPACOM to Megellan.
- Colonel Breteis,
Will you please get Dr.
Werhner out of the cabin?
I have a classified
message for you.
Scrambled cold
white, couple three.
- He's not in the cabin sir.
- Are you sure
that he can't hear?
- Why cheat sir.
- Colonel listen carefully,
make him a prisoner at once.
Take him alive if you can
but don't take any chances.
He isn't (mumbling)
He is a spy.
He plans to take
control of the Magellan,
and crush it into
the space station.
The FBI have just rescued
the real Dr. Werhner.
- Yes, sir we know.
- Repeat.
- Dr. Warner is dead.
You see, he did try
to take over the ship.
And Major Moore stopped him.
But in the struggle
the jets were fired
and I found it necessary
to land on the moon.
- You what?
- Repeat you did what?
- We had the land on the moon.
- Colonel, give me a channel
Pentagon immediately.
The Magellan has just
landed on the moon.
Colonel, report your
present situation in detail.
- Yes sir.
- Landed on Luna,
approximately 125 miles
back of crater Grimaldi
and approximately 10 miles
beyond the Terminator.
(mumbling)
- Anybody hurt?
- Only fatality, dr. Wherner.
He died during the establishment
of the radio relay,
11 miles from my
prison position.
This relay is the means
through which we've established
contact with you.
- Are you in any
immediate danger?
- No sir.
- The boredom is getting out.
- I'll call you in
exactly 60 minutes.
(upbeat music)
Straight comm to Magellan,
general Green speaking.
- [Joel] You're wasting your
life in front of that TV.
- Yes General, Morris speaking,
Colonel Breteis standing by sir.
- Good.
Now pay attention Bill.
Now that you two are on
the moon, stay there.
Do you understand?
- Yes General.
- That's easy.
- Pay attention and
don't interrupt.
The joint chiefs have
conferred with the president
and it's been decided
to change your mission.
You are now moon
base ,number one
you'll remain where you are
and show the flag
until such time
that you can be relieved
by a larger permanent fall.
- Show the flag to who?
- In the mean time rushen
your water, food and air
to last at least 10 days.
That's within safe limits
based on what you had.
And we'll undertake to
get all our supplies
over to you in that time.
connell you've had
drone pilot experience.
Bill, you've read board
your ship's radio equipment
to prevent it to jockey
supply rockets down.
- Now we don't have
anything better to do.
- I better be able to.
- I have one of the electronic
pushing boys advise you on.
I know it can be done and
they've already told me so.
Album based number one,
but don't go away Bill.
Ooh Connell.
I have a classified
message, from major Moore,
would you be psychiatrists to
go after and close the hatch?
- You heard what he
said, down below?
- Very well, sir,
if you say so.
- She just put her
hands over her ears ago.
La la la la la la.
- Oh, Bill
it's Grammy, Cody and combo two.
- Yes, sir.
We're not clear.
Standing by on scramble.
Yes sir.
Hey golf, you ranked son.
This is man to man
(laughs)
- Mano o mano.
- Let's do it.
I will share with
you and Breteis.
You're still sure of it.
- No.
- Good thing she went below.
- Seems to be,
you used to be pretty
sweet on her way back when.
- Yeah nice kid
kind nosy though.
- Tell me the truth
Bill, I got it all.
- Could it be that you're
still sweet on her?
Tell me the truth or
don't answer at all.
- He's not dr. Bellow.
He's dr. Chuck Woolery.
- Puppy what are you driving at?
- No, no.
- Don't get shirty son.
I don't like crying to your
face any more than you like it.
But I've just been talking
with the white house.
The president
thinks and so do I.
- The president thinks
that's something new.
- Y'all gotta be
shot in that tin can,
with a pretty young woman
for weeks, maybe months,
Public opinion,
being what it is.
It'd be a lot
better for everyone.
For country, for the
service and for you,
if you two were married.
- What are you
saying? I'm no rabbit.
- I can't give you
an order on this,
but think it over.
- Listen puppy.
She wouldn't have me
on a silver platter.
- How about in a tin can?
- Are sure?
- How about an air mattress,
slathered with butter?
- Oh, sorry.
- But you don't understand.
She has no use for me.
- Have you tried asking her?
- Yeah, I never thought of that.
- May I come up now?
It's lonely down here.
- Oh sure.
I was just going to tell you
that the general was through.
- And so are my
wild bachelor days.
- What did he say?
- Say it.
- Ask her.
- Go on.
- Nothing.
- Go on and ask her.
- Don't be a pansy.
- Ask her.
- Say it.
- Cool, cool, cool, cool. Cool.
- I was wondering
if you could...
- Could what Bill?
- I mean could you...
- Yes yes
- Ohh Germany.
- Ohh skip it .
We'll take it up later.
(mumbling)
(beep)
- Well they must have to
watch a middle eclipse or so.
- What is that?
- This looks like an
early version of Porn.
- Kinda ruban you know.
- Yeah.
- Ooh it's no fun at all.
- Oh no fun at all.
Look at Florida.
- Crashed is more like it.
- Bill it landed.
- Yeah, I'll go and
see what's in it.
- It's the minister.
- It looks like an
Interstellar or dunk tank.
- Wells Fargo rocket is
coming down a street.
- He's called for the
breaking fastball.
- I got a rocket full of staff
and I'm gonna go
get it, yes yes yes
- Now remember,
never attempt to remove
the bees from the hive
without proper protective gear.
- Yeah. It looks like a V too.
- Yeah, he could have had a V.
- I'm sorry.
- And it's filled with cat food.
- This rocket
was supposed to go to the
cat women at the moon.
- Well, let's see
what we got here.
- One 45 caliber handgun,
four clips of ammunition.
$100 in gold coin,
two packages of chewing gum
two issue Prophylactic shoot.
Gac could have a pretty good
time in Vegas with this stuff.
- No butter.
- They all say occupant.
- No expense was
spared in spring.
This cardboard box is gold.
- Bills, bills, bills.
- Bill, did they dend
everything We need?
- Breteis, it's Christmas.
- They're all bills.
- Oh, wait. That's me.
- Lots and lots of SPACOM.
- Hey, it's giant Rubik's cube.
- I love the smell of
SPACOM in the morning.
It smells like chicory.
- If you can solve this puzzle,
you can get married.
Then try solve that puzzle.
- Moon base to SPACOM.
Come in please.
SPACOM to lunar base.
- I want to talk to general
green on a secure channel.
Colonel Bright Eye speaking.
- Yes. Mum,
scrambled code F combo one.
- Had a minif on a raft.
- What is it Breteis?
Any trouble?
- No.
- Only with the invitations,
but we got them out in time.
- But you know we
promised to do something.
- Yes.
And a good thing too.
What about it?
- Well, if you expect me
to go through with it,
there's something
you've got to do for me.
- No I'm not going to
emcee your wedding.
- Well, at this point,
you can just about
write your own ticket,
if I can do it,
why does it kid?
- Well it's this.
- Dearly beloved,
we are gathered together
here on the side of God--
- And that's the tee shirt
or mom got married in.
- Do you take this woman to
be your lawfully wedded wife,
to have a new hold ,
to love and to cherish,
in sickness and in health
till death do you part?
- I do.
- Do you take this man to be
your lawfully wedded husband,
to have and to hold,
to love honor and obey
in sickness and in health
till death do you part?
- Or until the oxygen wears out.
- Who giveth this woman?
- I give this woman.
- You have no right
to give that woman.
- Take her left hand,
place the ring upon her fingure.
- Where did he get the ring?
- By the power invested in me,
I pronounce you man and wife.
- When you're a not a public?
- Mmh! Juicy fruit!
- Don't go, wait kids.
The president of
the United States,
wants to speak to you.
- I wonder what
he'll have to say.
- Can you hear me?
- No, no, no. Put the
president on, not his wife.
- We have a wedding
present for you,
From the people
of United States.
And my recommendation--
- It's dr. Ruth.
- Look you are on to air.
- You are today promoted to
the rank of Brigadier general,
United States space boss.
You will consider yourself
detached from USS Magellan.
- It's very healthy
to be in a capsule
together with your friends.
- US home based number one.
The guard who protects it.
For the benefit of all
the free peoples of it.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, speed it up.
We got some things
we want to get to.
- Yeah we got lives.
(somber music)
- Yeah, honey, I got you
blazing throwing star.
- You like you
wedding present dear?
- And I didn't get you ready.
- What!
- That's it.
- That was great!
But wait,
Ooh , Pathetic!
(somber music)
- Ooh we finally got
through that one.
Hey, thanks everybody for
your cards and letters,
they really helped
pull us through.
- Yeah, We thought the Lord
was going to call Joel home
until we got this card.
- Yeah I come back crucial
picture this one can...
- Cro you want to
read down one buddy?
Yeah. It says, please send us
info on the MST 3000 fan club.
We enjoyed it very much. Thanks.
Happy holidays from
the both of us.
Wou Look at these sweets.
- You know how they say?
When people get married,
they start looking alike.
These two have been
together a long time.
- My turn, my turn.
- Okay let her go.
Mr. Tom servo there.
- Right you are sloppy.
- This one comes
from a Jeff Conrad,
in Bloomington, Minnesota.
- Greetings
I've been a long time fan of
mystery science theater, 3000,
a group of friends and I watch
it every week on videotape.
Hey, tell me why the new show
is being colored
around black and white.
Sincerely Jeff Conrad.
- Well, and we got this last
one here from fabulous Hawaii.
- Wou!
- And it says, dear sirs I'd
like to join your fan club.
Please send me information.
Membership cards,
large sums of money.
Very funny.
That's from Sam lit
singer from Honolulu.
Oh yeah.
Tom servo, Why don't you
read that information
for the people on,
- Put it up there Camba.
Give it to me one
time on the CG,
A Helvetica bold.
Will you?
All right.
The mystery science
Theater 300 Fan Club
P.O.Box 5324
Hopkins, Minnesota
Send your cards and
letters quickly.
- All right. I guess that
ends the experiment sirs.
When are we going to
get some color movies?
- Color?
- You want color,
talk to Ted Turner.
Here file this.
- Consider that file.
- Well, hostel away go for
now my little Spud bunny.